I have a handful of slides here I want
我要几张幻灯片
to share with you and then we're going
与您分享，然后我们要
to dive into some real code and it's
深入研究一些真实的代码，
it's about building app management tools
这是关于构建应用程序管理工具
using the screen blue platform well now
现在很好地使用蓝色屏幕平台
you've done it
你已经做到了
you wouldn't built the perfect
你不会建立完美的
applications now everybody loves it your
应用程序现在每个人都喜欢它
your team was it because you'd be
你的团队是因为你会
architected it well you know use good
很好的架构，你知道用的很好
practices good tools instead of a lot
练习好的工具，而不是很多
like that the customer really loves it
这样的客户真的很喜欢
and the side effect of that is your
副作用就是你
manager loves it because you're bringing
经理喜欢它，因为您带来了
a lot of a lot of new business and a lot
很多新业务和很多
of the revenues so what can you expect
的收入，那么您能期望什么
as the outcome of that are you going to
结果就是你要
receive a promotion and climb the ladder
获得晋升并登上阶梯
maybe you're going to get a good pay
也许你会得到高薪
raise I think we know the answer to that
提高，我认为我们知道答案
one no you're not instead you get to
一个不，你不是，而是你去
support the app in tops so the time when
在顶部支持应用程序，因此时间
you'll probably have to you know your
您可能需要知道您的
manager will ask you to go out to the
经理会请你出去
sysadmin to the DevOps team and support
sysadmin对DevOps团队和支持
it in deployment and add some new
它在部署中并添加一些新的
support tools and things like that so
支持工具之类的东西
let's look at the let's compare two
让我们来看看让我们比较两个
different things the tool set they used
他们使用的不同工具集
to build the app with what what kind of
用什么样的方式构建应用
things did you use well you probably use
你用得很好的东西
Java or groovy assuming the audience
Java或groovy假定观众
it's probably tuned into this webinar
它可能已调入此网络研讨会
I'm assuming you've used some spring
我假设你已经用了一些春天
hopefully the new spring boot that's
希望新的 spring boot 是
that's been really hot and raging apache
真的很热，阿帕奇
tomcat
雄猫
various other parts of the spring tomcat
春季雄猫的其他各个部位
stack if you build some you know
如果您构建一些就可以堆叠
web-based front-end you're certainly
基于网络的前端，您肯定
using HTML Javascript CSS 3 I'll call
我将使用HTML Javascript CSS 3
that goodness and probably usually maven
这种善良，也许通常是行家
or Gradle it's cats so like 85% of Java
或Gradle是猫，就像Java的85％
projects use maven and Grails coming in
项目使用Maven和Grails进来
second that's getting a lot of
第二，越来越多
popularity however when you go over and
受欢迎但是当你过去
start building some tools to support
开始构建一些工具来支持
your app and to manage it and gather
您的应用程序并对其进行管理和收集
metrics and do all kinds of that stuff
指标并做各种各样的事情
what what kind of tools do you hear
您听到什么样的工具
people using they're often you hear
人们经常听到他们的声音
about different shell scripting tools
关于不同的shell脚本工具
and here I kind of have a joke that
我在这里开个玩笑
there's almost a shell for every letter
每个字母几乎都有一个外壳
of the alphabet available
可用的字母
if you're a test fit and script junkie
如果您适合测试和脚本迷
like myself you may use tools like
像我一样，您可以使用类似的工具
Python or tickle pique and expect some
Python或挠痒痒的皮毛，期待一些
you might use things like Ruby there's
您可能会使用Ruby之类的东西
some older tools like parole or T sequel
一些较旧的工具，例如假释或T续集
for writing the tools and very support
用于编写工具和非常支持
scripts and you know basically just
脚本，你基本上知道
about any kind of scripting language
关于任何一种脚本语言
that you can imagine I've seen
你可以想象我已经看到
proprietary tools that came with certain
某些工具随附的专有工具
stacks that I was able to utilize in my
我可以利用的堆栈
career so what does this amount to if
事业，这意味着什么
you need to do something like connect to
您需要执行诸如连接到
Facebook you know you need your tool to
Facebook，您知道您需要使用工具
access Facebook and do something or look
访问Facebook并做某事或外观
at Twitter or github this presentation
在Twitter或github上的演示
we're going to look at a support tool
我们将看一个支持工具
that actually taps into github what if
实际上是进入github的，如果
you need your your toolset to connect to
您需要您的工具集才能连接到
RabbitMQ you know perhaps your your main
RabbitMQ，您可能知道您的主要
production application is using that
生产应用程序正在使用
RabbitMQ broker and which is at a recent
RabbitMQ经纪人，最近
study showing 1 million messages a
研究显示一百万条信息
second of steady processing and you want
稳定处理的秒数，您要
to write a support script to tap into
编写支持脚本以利用
some of that and gather symmetric data
其中一些并收集对称数据
what if you want to connect into the
如果您想连接到
database that the main app is running
主应用程序正在运行的数据库
against or what if you need to you know
反对，或者如果您需要知道该怎么办
if you're not using RabbitMQ pressure
如果您不使用RabbitMQ压力
using JMS messaging and you want to hook
使用JMS消息传递，并且您想挂钩
into some of that and measure flow or
进入其中一些并测量流量或
things like that you know or potentially
您知道或潜在的事情
do you want to reuse part of your apps
您想重用部分应用程序吗
modules well if you're using something
如果您使用的东西模块很好
like Python you have to go learn a
像Python，您必须去学习
different library a different you know
不同的图书馆，你知道的不同
component access all these features you
组件访问所有这些功能
may not even be able to access something
甚至可能无法访问某些内容
like JMS through through these tools and
通过这些工具，像JMS
what you're going to use a J Python or
您将使用J Python或
guy phone I mean so you know it's a it's
家伙电话，我是说，所以你知道这是一个
a struggle with that and so you know my
与之斗争，所以你知道我的
question I asked and we're going to
我问的问题，我们将要
explore in this webinar is why not use
在此网络研讨会中探讨的是为什么不使用
the same set of tools for both and my
与我和我相同的工具集
reaction to that would be I think that
我对此的反应是
would be totally awesome being able to
能够真的很棒
have my tools with Java or especially
使用我的工具或Java
the def programming language of groovy
groovy的def编程语言
it's very appealing if I'm able to use
如果我能够使用的话，这非常吸引人
spring plus Tomcat for both in real
Spring和Tomcat结合使用
simple and clear-cut ways that would be
简单明了的方式
stupendous and then we're also going to
太棒了，然后我们还要
dig in and look at spring boots CLI
深入了解一下弹簧靴CLI
tool and then finally some you know HTML
工具，最后一些您知道的HTML
and all of its supported features so to
及其所有受支持的功能，以便
do that we're going to go visit a a few
这样做，我们将去拜访一些
a few apps we there's a couple apps that
一些应用程序我们有几个应用程序
we that I put together to help support
我一起帮助支持我们
stuff last summer over the span of about
去年夏天的东西大约
three or four months
三四个月
Roy Clarkson Craig walls and myself
罗伊·克拉克森·克雷格（Roy Clarkson Craig）墙壁和我自己
wrote about fifty fifty or so getting
写了大约五十点左右
started guides that are now at that
现在开始的指南
springs website each of those getting
斯普林斯网站每个人
started guides is hosted on a separate
入门指南分别托管
github repository and we encourage
github存储库，我们鼓励
people if you spot a bug in the code if
人们，如果您发现代码中的错误，如果
you spot a typo please go and open an an
您发现错字了，请打开
issue at that github repository
在那个github仓库发布
until we can track it down well the idea
直到我们能够很好地找到想法
of navigating 50 different github
导航50个不同的github的过程
repository set the issues is a nightmare
存储库设置问题是一场噩梦
and we quickly ran into that as you know
正如您所知，我们很快就遇到了
we nothing is perfect and we had to
我们没有什么是完美的，我们不得不
start tracking it so I'm gonna open up
开始跟踪它，所以我要打开
my browser here and show you a tool that
我的浏览器在这里，并向您显示一个工具
we built called issue aggregator and
我们建立了所谓的问题汇总器
here what we have is this is a little
这是我们有的一点
app that I wrote or a support script if
我编写的应用或支持脚本（如果有）
you will and its job is to go visit all
你会的，它的工作是去拜访所有人
the guides that we have on github and
我们在github和
look up all their open issues and
查找他们所有未解决的问题，
actually now we have over 60 guides this
实际上，现在我们有60多个指南
is this is not bad for the number of
这对于数量来说还不错吗
open issues against the guides so but
根据指南公开问题，所以，但是
periodically maybe about every two weeks
定期大约每两周一次
I want to come in and try to clean up
我想进去尝试清理
some of the outstanding issues to make
一些悬而未决的问题
things to make it better and so this is
事情要变得更好，所以这是
much faster than trying to go to
比尝试去要快得多
something like this I'm going to
这样的事情我要去
navigate to each guide go to navigate to
导航到每个指南，然后转到
each of the issues and check are there
每个问题并检查是否存在
any issues here so why don't we go open
这里有任何问题，为什么我们不开放
up this app that I built called issue
我建立的这个应用程式叫问题
aggregator and take a look at it I'm
聚合器，看看它，我是
going to zoom it in here so it's a more
要在这里放大它，所以更多
readable so with this
可读性如此
is this is a I just do a quick scroll
这是我只是快速滚动
through it's really not a lot of code we
通过它，实际上我们并没有很多代码
walk through the bits of it here this is
穿过它的位，这是
a groovy this is a groovy file you know
groovy，这是您知道的groovy文件
at the top of us I put it into a package
在我们的顶部，我把它放在一个包装里
we're making use of groovy grape which
我们正在使用普通葡萄
lets us pull in dependencies and what
让我们引入依赖关系以及什么
this does is this says I don't need a
这就是说我不需要
build file I don't need a project
构建文件，我不需要项目
structure I can just write a single file
我可以只写一个文件的结构
and I have an app and in this case we're
我有一个应用，在这种情况下，
going to use spring social github and J
将使用spring social github和J
soup you'll see why I did a little down
汤，你会明白为什么我有点失望
further I have a few import statements
此外，我有一些进口声明
the fact that I'm using spring boot CLI
我正在使用Spring Boot CLI的事实
saves me from a lot of the import
使我免于大量进口
statements that I might need such as
我可能需要的陈述，例如
spring MVC or Jackson I don't need to
春季MVC或Jackson，我不需要
use those import statements because boot
使用这些导入语句，因为启动
will provide them for me automatically
会自动为我提供
and that's what happens in cities down
那就是在城市低谷发生的事情
here you can see I'm pulling in some
在这里你可以看到我在拉一些
other dependencies using the shorthand
使用速记的其他依赖项
notation that blue provides we're going
蓝色表示我们要去的符号
to have some time the thyme leaves
有一段时间百里香离开
templates and spring web components and
模板和Spring Web组件以及
Jackson for data bindings this class
Jackson用于数据绑定的此类
which I can just almost squeeze into a
我几乎可以挤成一个
page here it's called issue aggregator
此处称为问题汇总器的页面
in fact it's a spring MVC controller and
实际上，这是一个Spring MVC控制器，
I also have it use the groovy at log
我也有在日志中使用groovy
annotation so I can have a logger
注释，这样我就可以拥有一个记录器
embedded inside this code automatically
自动嵌入到此代码中
without having to set it up now two
现在不必设置两个
things that you have to have in order to
您必须具备的东西
connect to github and look up open
连接到github并查找打开
issues is you actually need to have an
问题是您实际上需要拥有一个
access token this is a password that yet
访问令牌，这是一个密码
to configure in the later on after the
在以后的配置中
webinar if you go visit the project
网络研讨会（如果您要访问该项目）
which I'll show you it has all the steps
我会告诉你它具有所有步骤
and how to create your own token we also
以及如何创建自己的令牌
need to tell that which particular
需要告诉哪个特别
organization we wanted to look at and by
我们想要研究的组织
default it's going to look at spring
默认情况下，它会看春天
guides here we've configured a being
指南在这里我们已经配置了一个存在
we're creating a new github template
我们正在创建一个新的github模板
we're plugging into github token value
我们正在插入github令牌值
other words our password and because I
换句话说我们的密码，因为我
actually want to use the template right
实际想使用模板的权利
here in this code I need the auto wire
在这段代码中，我需要自动接线
and grab an instance of it now this
并抓住它的一个实例
method right here is sort of the gold of
这里的方法有点像
the whole thing of what it does
它所做的全部事情
it's it's said a list of repository
就是说仓库清单
names basically string so what it does
名称基本上是字符串，所以它做什么
is it's going to iterate over them and
是要遍历他们，
generate and collect them together for
生成并收集它们在一起
each repository it's going to take the
每个存储库都需要
github template grab the get the repo
github模板获取获取回购
operations and look up issues for that
操作并为此查找问题
organization and repository and what
组织和存储库以及什么
it's going to do it's going to apply a
将要执行的操作
filter right here it's going to filter
过滤器在这里它将要过滤
out and only grab the ones that are open
出去，只抓住那些开放的
after that I put a little polish and had
在那之后我放了一点抛光剂
it sort by the number of the item and
按项目编号排序
then finally transform it into have each
然后最终将其转化为拥有
entry transformed into a tiny dictionary
词条变成了一个小小的字典
with both the repository name and the
带有存储库名称和
github issue itself and the issue is the
github问题本身，问题是
is a gif is a spring social github issue
是gif是春季社交github问题
and the the fact that the issue itself
以及问题本身的事实
doesn't hold the repository name as why
不保存存储库名称的原因
I needed to grab it and put it here
我需要把它放到这里
now all that stuff I'm going to do a
现在我要做的所有事情
quick check and say if it is more than
快速检查并说是否超过
you know if it's not empty then flatten
你知道它是否不为空然后展平
it out into a simple list for me to
列出一个简单的清单给我
process now
现在处理
down here is where I actually have a
在这里，我实际上有一个
spring MVC route mapped I'm going to map
Spring MVC路线映射，我要映射
it to up to the root page here and what
它到这里的根页面以及什么
it's going to do it's going to go
它会去做它会去做
connect with j-su to spring about iOS
与j-su交流以了解iOS
flash guides let's go pull that up and
闪光指南让我们将其拉起
look at what that but that page is this
看看那是什么，那是这个页面
is where you can go and find the list of
在这里您可以找到清单
all the guides that we've built and
我们构建的所有指南以及
essentially it's going to go scan each
从本质上讲，将要扫描每个
of them if I if I go view this on the
他们，如果我去看这个
backside right here I'm happen to be
背面在这里我碰巧是
looking at class a class ID title with
看着班级的班级ID标题
the href here this is the path to the
这里的href是通往
path of a guide that I'm interested in
我感兴趣的指南的路径
so if I go back to the code but I was
所以如果我回到代码，但是
done here's all such that entire page
这样就完成了整个页面
and ideas I want to go grab every one of
我想去的想法和想法
those so that I can dynamically pick up
这些，以便我可以动态地接起来
all the guides that are currently out
目前所有的指南
there and what J soup does is it's a
在那里，J汤的作用是
library a Java library that provides a
库Java库提供
jQuery like selector syntax I can do
jQuery就像我可以做的选择器语法
select and I'm looking for that a dot
选择，我正在寻找一个点
guide title
指导标题
touken now inside it I have a filter I
现在里面的刀剑我有一个过滤器
do not want any event Ruiz that there
不想任何事件鲁伊斯那里
were actually tutorials instead this app
实际上是教程，而不是这个应用程序
is focused on this moment managing the
专注于此刻管理
guides and then once I have that
指导，然后一旦我有那个
filtered list I'm gonna do a
筛选清单，我要
transformation basically I need to take
基本上我需要采取的转变
that HR F value that we had here it had
我们在这里拥有的HR F值
slash guide /gs last scheduling tasks
斜杠指南/ gs最后的调度任务
TAS I want to take the href I'm gonna
TAS我想接受href我
subtract out slash guides last GX that
减去最后一个GX的斜杠
was in the front of the string and I'm
在弦的前面，我是
going to subtract the flash at the end
最后要减去闪光
of the string and then I'm gonna prefix
的字符串，然后我要加前缀
it with GS so this is where you get a
GS，所以这是您得到的地方
tap your groovy magic and use you know
点击您的常规魔术，并使用您知道的
what scripting tools have if you were to
如果要使用什么脚本工具
write this in Java I feel like this
用Java写这个我感觉像这样
would be a pain in the neck to try to
试图去脖子上会很痛苦
put together this kind of string
把这种弦放在一起
operations but with groovy it's a piece
操作，但具有常规性
of cake and then finally what I'm going
蛋糕，然后我要去的东西
to do is I'll built up this array of
我要做的是建立这个数组
repository issues I'm gonna put them
我要放的仓库问题
into my spring MVC model and return back
进入我的春季MVC模型并返回
until the tell it to render the home
直到告诉它渲染房屋
view I go take a peek at that we try
看我去看看我们尝试
that here we go now this is the web page
现在我们去这里是网页
that that I've built and we're not going
我建立的，我们不会去的
to walk through every line but if you've
遍历每一行，但如果您已经
done any web development you may
完成了您可能进行的任何Web开发
recognize that this is generally a
认识到这通常是
bootstrap Twitter or sorry a Twitter
引导Twitter或对Twitter感到抱歉
bootstrap CSS layout and what I've
引导CSS布局以及我所拥有的
actually done is for styling I wouldn't
实际要做的是样式，我不会
grab the style sheets directly right off
立即获取样式表
of spring bio so that it has a familiar
春天的生物，所以它有一个熟悉的
look and feel for managing the stuff I
外观和感觉来管理我的东西
scroll down here to where the content is
向下滚动到内容所在的位置
it's basically a giant table structure
它基本上是一个巨大的表结构
that I have and right in the center of
我拥有的就在中心
it is where I'm going to actually
这是我要去的地方
iterate over all those issues now this
现在遍历所有这些问题
is a this is a time leaf template this
这是时间模板
is not a JSP because I find JSP is
不是JSP，因为我发现JSP是
unwieldy this hard to manage and I've
笨拙这很难管理，我已经
been able to get a lot more efficiently
能够更有效地获取
written templates and stuff using timely
及时使用书面模板和材料
so here I'm going to iterate over each
所以在这里我要遍历每个
issue and then I'm going to basically
问题，然后我将基本上
extract the name of the repository and
提取存储库的名称，然后
then I'm gonna also grab the issue and
然后我还要抓住这个问题，
then look up this HTML URL address so
然后查找此HTML URL地址，以便
you can hyperlink jump to it
您可以超链接跳转到它
and then finally I'm gonna print up you
最后我要打印你
know who's it assigned to and if it's
知道分配给谁以及是否
not if it's not assigned anybody then
如果没有分配任何人，则不会
just leave it empty or leave it as
只是将其留空或保留为
unassigned and then finally what's the
未分配，然后最后是什么
title of the issue you know with all
大家都知道的问题的标题
that basically it lets me render this
基本上它可以让我渲染这个
here so from this app I can quickly look
在这里，所以从这个应用程序，我可以快速查看
and see well there's three open issues
并很好地看到三个未解决的问题
against the getting started guide for
反对的入门指南
messaging rhetta's if I click here
如果我单击此处，则发送消息的rhetta
that's github hideous a record for it
那是github令人毛骨悚然的记录
and I can quickly navigate to the issue
我可以快速找到问题所在
and start to read it and digest and
并开始阅读并消化
figure out I solve it so you know to me
弄清楚我解决了，所以你对我知道
putting together that tiny amount of
放在一起
code which zoomed in zoomed in is like
放大的代码就像
barely fits you know it's page and a
几乎不适合您，它的页面和
half a code that lets me basically do my
一半的代码可以让我基本完成我的任务
job a lot easier and come in you know
工作容易得多，进来就知道
clean up clean up issues so that's our
清理清理问题，这就是我们的
first example and this is like all issue
第一个例子，这就像所有问题
aggregator and you can actually see the
聚合器，您实际上可以看到
code yourself if you want to over my
如果您想结束我的工作，请自行编码
github get up repository so if you go
github建立存储库，所以如果你去
visit here you can see it and get all
访问这里，您可以看到并获得所有
the information here about how to set it
有关如何设置的信息
up it shows you how to set up a github
它展示了如何设置github
token how to how to run it from the
令牌如何从
command lines and even how to upload it
命令行，甚至如何上传
to cloud foundry even though I think
即使我认为云铸造厂
those documents we've got a little bit
这些文件，我们有一点
out of date now there's a there's
现在已经过时了
another tool that I built also which
我建立的另一个工具
when I keep our eye on is a back up here
当我继续关注的时候，就在这里
and I'm going to go visit one of the
我要去参观其中之一
guides here this is something a few if
指导这里，这是一些如果
you've been able to see the guide since
从此您就可以看到该指南
we released them last year they've been
去年我们发布了它们
really handy for you to do stuff but you
对您来说确实很方便，但是您
know tells you how to how to solve a
知道告诉你如何解决
problem but you may not have noticed in
问题，但您可能没有注意到
the right-hand corner that we have an
我们有一个右角
icon that shows what the bill does pass
显示账单通过的图标
I click on that icon it actually takes
我点击它实际上需要的图标
me to dry Oh which is a CI server
我要干哦，这是CI服务器
solution atom on the lab and we actually
实验室中的解决方案原子，我们实际上
have a CI job every guide out there and
每个向导都有一份CI工作，
that is if it go if if we do something
那就是如果我们做某事的话
to the code and it breaks it want to
到代码，它破坏了它想要
know about it so here I'm looking at one
知道这一点，所以我在这里看着
particular guide I can go look at look
特别的指导我可以去看看
at their interface and see all the guys
在他们的界面上，看到所有的家伙
that we have and see that they're all
我们拥有的，看到他们都是
what their status is and if I scroll and
它们的状态是什么，如果我滚动并
scroll and scroll and keep scrolling I
滚动并滚动并继续滚动我
can finally see what the status of all
终于可以看到所有状态
of them are and while one of them's red
其中一个是红色的
so need to address it but this is an
因此需要解决，但这是一个
incredibly inefficient use of real
真实使用效率极低
estate on the screen for this many for
屏幕上的房地产为许多
such a large volume so I had an idea of
这么大的容量，所以我有一个想法
why not do the same tactic I did and
为什么不做和我一样的战术
create something call it drone
创建一个叫做无人机的东西
aggregator and get a more efficient
聚合器并获得更高的效率
there's that red one there I get a more
有那红色的那边我还有更多
a tighter view of it at a glance to see
一目了然地看到它
if everything what the status of all
如果一切都什么状态
guides are you know for each one of
您知道每一个指南
these there's a hyperlink here where I
这些在这里有一个超链接
can can easily navigate to the guide
可以轻松导航到指南
itself I want to look at it or I can see
本身我想看一下或者我可以看到
the if is where the icon is I can click
如果可以，我可以单击图标
on that and navigate to the drone job so
在那并导航到无人机工作，这样
both these things help me manage this
这两件事都帮助我解决了这个问题
stuff and I can actually jump I even put
东西，实际上我甚至可以跳
hyperlinks so that I can jump between
超链接，以便我可以在
both of these apps that I have now let's
我现在拥有的这两个应用程序
go look at the code for drone aggregator
去看看无人机聚合器的代码
and see what that looks like when you
看看你的样子
zoom it up here again we're going to use
再次放大到这里，我们将使用
chase soup it's we're gonna have time
追汤，这是我们要有时间
leaf and actually that's that's it
叶，实际上就是这样
that's the whole app right there it's
那就是整个应用程序
going to do the same trick it's going to
要做同样的技巧
connect the news Jay soup and connect
连接新闻周杰伦汤和连接
and look up all the names of the guides
并查找所有指南名称
this way dynamically will update the
这样动态地更新
page as we publish new guides and I
我们发布新指南时的页面
don't have to go update this app just
不必去更新此应用程序
just add any guide to it it's going to
只需添加任何指南，它将
do pretty much the same query to get the
做几乎相同的查询来获取
list of guy
家伙名单
to filter out all the tutorials this
过滤掉所有的教程
time the transformation is slightly
时间的转变是轻微的
different we're doing the same string
不同，我们在做相同的字符串
trickery to go extract out the actual
欺骗去提取实际
name of the guide as it appears but in
出现的指南名称，但在
the sense we're not we're not going to
感觉我们不是，我们不会
get hub we don't need spring social
获得中心，我们不需要春季社交
github because we're not looking at the
github，因为我们不在看
issues on github instead we're basically
github上的问题，相反，我们基本上
building two links for every project one
为每个项目建立两个链接
to go to the guide and want to go to its
去指南，想去它
drone see I jog the next case I want to
无人机看到我要慢跑下一个案例
grab the href and I'm also going to grab
抓住href，我也要抓住
the text of the title but underneath it
标题文字，但在标题下方
and then finally I'm going to take that
最后我要接受
information and I'm going to put it into
信息，我将其放入
my spring MVC model objects now in this
我的春季MVC模型对象现在在此
case what I did what I want to do is I
案例我做了我想做的是我
want to use a more Groovy's awesome
想要使用更多Groovy的超赞
collection support and basically take it
收集支持并基本接受
take an entire list of guides and chunk
拿完整的指南和清单
it up into the end of chunks of four
它一直到四个块的末尾
guides per row and this is - its collate
每行的指南，这是-它的整理
operation and return the home view and
操作并返回主视图
so all this maps onto our the flash
所以所有这些都映射到我们的闪光灯上
route I go pull that pull that up this
我去的路线
will look suspiciously just like the
看起来像
other one you know again I'm using the
另一个你又知道我正在使用
same styling sheet from spring Daioh
春天大同的相同样式表
itself just to give it a similar look
本身只是为了给它一个类似的外观
and feel you know you saw me navigating
感觉你知道你看到我在航行
on the navbar up at the top that's
在顶部的导航栏上
letting you hop over to issue aggregator
让您跳过以发布聚合器
and issue out great and lets me hop back
发出很棒的声音，让我跳回去
to drone aggregator down here I build up
在这里建立无人机聚合器
a similar table in this case for each
在这种情况下，每个
for each row that I build I'm going to
对于我建立的每一行，我将
take that the chunks and divvy it up
把那块切成薄片
into a single chunk and then now I need
成一个块，然后我需要
to make a separate divisional element so
做一个分开的划分元素
I'm going to iterate over the chunk and
我要遍历大块
get each individual guide now again this
现在再次获得每个单独的指南
is where I'm using time leaf as my
是我使用时间片作为我的地方
templating engine instead of JSP it
模板引擎而不是JSP
takes a little bit of ramped up time to
需要一点时间增加
get the hang of being able to assemble
掌握组装的窍门
strings but here I'm basically going to
字符串，但是我基本上要在这里
meld together spring do with the href
春季与href融合在一起
which would be the name of the guide to
这将是指南的名称
go to and this is and I'm going to plug
去，这是，我要插入
it in with the title
它带有标题
love it you know down below I need an
爱它，你知道下面我需要一个
alternate string where I'm going to
我要去的备用字符串
construct a go to drone i/o into the
在无人机上架设无人机
spring guide and put the name of the
春天指南，并把名字
guide and then take you to the latest
指导，然后带您到最新
job or show me the latest that will link
工作或给我看最新的链接
to the latest job and inside it I'm
到最新的工作，我在里面
going to have an image object and in
将有一个图像对象，并在
this case I'm going to link into the the
在这种情况下，我将链接到
image that we show on the guide itself
我们在指南本身上显示的图像
at the same image that's status dot PNG
在与状态点PNG相同的图像上
file and here's I ran out of options I
文件，这是我用尽了所有选项
wanted to be able to potentially like
希望能够喜欢
let me add up and put it let me put an
让我加起来并把它放进去
alert right at the top of the page that
在页面顶部提醒
says hey there's a guide down go check
说嘿，有个向导去检查一下
it out unfortunately they use the same
不幸的是，他们使用相同的
image icon status P&amp;G whether it's red
图像图标状态宝洁是否为红色
or green or you know up or down so I can
或绿色，或者您知道上下，所以我可以
show it on the screen but I can't read
在屏幕上显示它，但我看不懂
that it's a visual clue but in a
这是视觉线索，但在
nutshell you can go look at this code to
简而言之，您可以去看看这段代码
back up here and show you where it is on
回到这里，告诉你它在哪里
github under my github my dead hub
github在我的github下面我死了的中心
repository here for a drone aggregator
无人机聚集器的存储库
and you know this is all about how to
而且你知道这就是如何
slap together a quick tool to overcome a
拍拍快速工具克服
current situation you know I can
你知道我现在的情况
interact with the people developing
与发展中的人互动
drone and ask them to change their
无人机，并要求他们改变他们的
interface but they may you know I don't
界面，但他们可能您知道我不知道
have time to do that and I may they have
有时间这样做，我可能他们有
different reasons why they want to keep
他们为什么要保留的不同原因
the way it is so I can mash up their
这样我就可以混搭他们的
data and include my own links to it you
数据并包括我自己的链接到您
know and here you can figure out you can
知道，在这里你可以弄清楚你可以
check out the code and repurpose it for
签出代码并将其重新用于
your own means now I want to show one
你自己的意思，现在我想展示一个
more quick example before we do our
我们做之前的更快速的例子
coding exercise I've actually been
我实际上一直在进行编码练习
writing a book recently called learning
写一本书，最近叫做学习
spring boot and for that part of it is I
spring boot ，那是我
have a lot of these console outputs that
这些控制台输出很多
you see like basically in parts of the
您基本上会看到
code I want two parts of the book I want
代码，我想要这本书的两部分
to put this output to show you what this
把这个输出告诉你这是什么
output is way too wide to put into a
输出太宽，无法放入
book so I want to you know I wanted to
书，所以我想你知道我想
basically take all this stuff but let me
基本上把所有这些东西拿走，但是让我
strip out let me strip out this chunk
剥去让我去掉这块
from the output on a line by line basis
从输出逐行输出
this line exceeds 80 characters trim it
此行超过80个字符的行将其修剪
down and put an ellipsis on so what I
放下省略号，这样我
did was I instead of reaching for Python
是不是我而不是Python
until I've used for years I instead
直到我已经使用多年，
reached for spring boot and groovy to
达到了 spring boot 和常规
write this and I basically call it
写这个，我基本上称之为
cleanup boot console output what this
清理启动控制台输出什么
script is doing is it implements spring
脚本正在执行的是实现春天
boots command line runner so this is a
引导命令行运行程序，所以这是一个
you know this is a command line
你知道这是一个命令行
interface this doesn't have a web layer
没有网络层的界面
to it and this need to have to implement
为此，这需要实施
the run method this going to do is going
这将要运行的运行方法
to parse the Java system dot in property
解析属性中的Java系统点
and iterate over it line by line I have
然后逐行遍历
this line in order that I can extract
这条线，以便我可以提取
the timestamp it's a regular expression
时间戳记是一个正则表达式
the parse the timestamp the beginning of
解析时间戳记的开始
the line if it if it is a timestamp you
如果是时间戳记，则为该行
know and if so based on the size of it
根据其大小知道是否
if it's over 80 characters then I'm just
如果超过80个字符，那么我就是
gonna trim it back to 77 characters and
将其修剪回77个字符，
the three dots at the end otherwise I'll
最后的三个点，否则我会
just wrap the whole line and if it's not
只需将整行换行，如果不是
a time state if it's not a timestamp at
时间状态（如果不是时间戳记）
all then I'm gonna trim it down and just
然后我要把它修剪下来
look at the 80 characters to trim it out
看一下80个字符来修剪
me I'm gonna go test that so I've gotten
我，我要去测试，所以我已经
let me pick and pick a bigger fragment
让我挑一个更大的碎片
okay so here's like an output that I
好吧，这就像我的输出
captured and this just doesn't fit on
捕获了，这不适合
the screen but but I wrote this little
屏幕，但我写了一点
script so when I run it through here
脚本，所以当我在这里运行它时
it's going to launch the Springwood CLI
这将启动Springwood CLI
and here it's going to take that it's
在这里，它将是
going to take the input of that file and
将接受该文件的输入，然后
run it through my terminal and it's
通过我的终端运行它
going to cut it down and it'll be no
要减少它，它将是没有
more than 80 characters wide and then I
超过80个字符，然后我
can take that text and paste it into my
可以将文本粘贴到我的
manuscript now they just recently
现在手稿，他们只是最近
released this morning spring boot one
今早发布的 spring boot 一
dot one dot four and they added a
点一个点四，他们增加了一个
feature that I I asked for it may not be
II要求的功能可能不是
really big on everybody's plate but it's
在每个人的盘子上都非常大，但是
important to me is they added the quiet
对我来说重要的是他们增加了安静
flag so when you run the script you can
标记，以便在运行脚本时可以
now turn on the quiet flag and it will
现在打开安静标志，它将
not print out all this extra logging
没有打印出所有这些额外的日志
output from spring boot itself
弹簧靴本身的输出
see all I you know it comes to spreading
看到我所知道的关于传播的一切
scripts all I want is what the script
我想要的脚本就是脚本
itself is outputting which is just the
本身就是输出
stuff right here so I'm eager to upgrade
东西在这里，所以我渴望升级
to that you know so here's where I've
你知道，所以这是我去过的地方
been able to go write some little tools
能够去写一些小工具
to support myself now the last tool
现在支持自己的最后一个工具
we're going to look at today is a want
我们今天要看的是
to call spring monitor I want to
给我想要的弹簧监控器打电话
describe a scenario that actually worked
描述实际可行的方案
on in the past we had a system that
过去我们有一个系统
would gather weather data and we gather
会收集天气数据，我们会收集
it in periodic cycles like lightning
它像闪电一样周期性地循环
data would collect every 30 seconds and
数据将每30秒收集一次，并且
Doppler radar data would collect every 2
多普勒雷达数据每2个收集一次
minutes and my job was to take the data
分钟，我的工作是获取数据
files and move them to the other weather
文件并将其移至其他天气
stations automatically but I will always
自动站，但我会一直
log every time I process the data file
每次处理数据文件时记录日志
and I discovered later on down the road
我后来发现在路上
that I could write a script to pull the
我可以写一个脚本来拉
log files and detect well my teammate is
记录文件并很好地检测我的队友是
supposed to be every 30 seconds but I
应该是每30秒一次，但我
haven't seen one for two minutes
两分钟没见过
and so I would build a screen that would
所以我会建立一个屏幕
turn red when that happened and it would
当发生这种情况时变成红色，它将
tip me off and I need to go fix the
给我小费，我需要去修理
process so what I'm going to pull up
过程，所以我要拉起
here is a this is going to simulate a
这是一个要模拟的
production app imagine this imagine this
生产应用程序想象这个想象这个
is the perfect app that you just built
是您刚刚构建的完美应用
you know it's job is to collect things
你知道工作是收集东西
like lightning data now this is a spring
就像闪电的数据，现在是春天
boots EOI app but it doesn't have to be
引导EOI应用程序，但不一定要
it could be you know could be a giant
可能是你知道可能会成为一个巨人
monolithic production app that you build
您构建的整体生产应用程序
for demonstration purposes it's using
出于演示目的，它正在使用
Springs scheduling support and it's
Springs调度支持，
scheduled to do this every five seconds
计划每五秒钟执行一次
it will basically all it's going to do
基本上它将要做的一切
it's going to log out a message and say
这将注销一条消息并说
simulated activity simulated activity
模拟活动模拟活动
and down here I have another job that
在这里，我还有另一项工作
happens every three seconds and it's
每三秒钟发生一次
going to generate a weather forecast
将要生成天气预报
every two seconds now you know these
现在每两秒钟你就知道这些
numbers are made up for demo purposes
数字是出于演示目的
but let me go run it to give you an idea
但让我去运行它给你一个想法
what this looks like now if I just I run
如果我跑步我现在看起来像什么
my app here what it's going to start
我的应用程序将要开始
doing on the right hand side of the
在右手边做
screen it's printing out we see
屏幕正在打印出来，我们看到
lightning data weather forecast and it's
闪电数据天气预报
login it's traffic and it also has a
登录它的流量，它也有一个
stamp on the left hand side and what I'm
左边印有我的名字
interested in is being able to grab the
感兴趣的是能够抓住
time stamp and compare it to now to see
时间戳并将其与现在比较以查看
if it's it's it's a date has gone out of
如果它是一个日期已经过了
date number one car I need to do one
日期一号车我需要做一辆
extra step and that's actually I want to
额外的步骤，这实际上是我想要的
drop it into a log file so in this case
将其放入日志文件中，因此在这种情况下
it's going to print it to the console
它将打印到控制台
and it's going to generate a log file
它将生成一个日志文件
for me to process so I'm going to let
给我处理，所以我要让
that run in the background and now let's
在后台运行，现在让我们
look at the monitor app that the support
看一下显示器应用程序的支持
app that I want to build so the purpose
我想要构建的应用程序
of this app is I want to go monitor the
这个程序的我想去监视
log file
日志文件
I want to detect if it's either
我想检测是否
currently generating data and meaning
当前生成数据和含义
the system is in a good state or if it
系统处于良好状态，或者
is stopped generating data beating it
停止生成击败它的数据
switch to a bad state and tip somebody
切换到不良状态并提示某人
off so to do this I have this app has
关闭，为此，我有这个应用程序
four components in it I'm not going to
其中的四个部分我不会
go into details about the import
详细了解导入
statements these are basically the
这些基本上是
imports that I need to use this stuff
我需要使用这些东西的进口
down here the first chunk I want to talk
在这里，我想谈的第一部分
about is the monitor basically I was
基本上我是显示器
trying to figure out a way to pull a log
试图找出一种方法来拉日志
file and entail as new lines got added
文件，并且需要添加新行
to it and it occurred to me that perhaps
发生在我身上，也许
spring integration and had that ability
春季整合，并具有这种能力
so I called up Gary Russell who's the
所以我打电话给加里·罗素（Gary Russell）
spring is the lead for spring
春天是春天的先导
integration and we chatted for about
整合，我们聊了一下
five minutes about this and he told me
五分钟，他告诉我
oh all you need is this little guy here
哦，你需要的是这个小家伙
OS delegating file tailing message
操作系统委派文件尾消息
producer you create an instance you
生产者，您创建实例
configure the file it's going to watch
配置将要观看的文件
and here I'm pointing it at send log
这里我将其指向发送日志
which has being generated as we speak
当我们说话的时候
and you also configure its output
并且您还配置了它的输出
Channel so here I'm pointing it at tail
通道，所以在这里我将其指向尾巴
channel which is a spring integration
弹簧整合通道
direct channel and then I return this
直接渠道，然后我返回
beam to get picked up by the application
光束被应用拾取
context so all this all this classes job
上下文，所以所有这些类工作
is to monitor for new lines being added
监视要添加的新行
to the log files and as they happen
到日志文件以及发生的情况
publish into a spring integration
发布到春季集成
channel now downstream I have another
现在下游通道我有另一个
thing and monitor service I'm going to
我要去的东西和监控服务
kind of
的种类
around a bit and not trying to make it
大概不做
too confusing here to follow our flow of
在这里太混乱了，无法跟随我们的流程
action here and they previously were
在这里行动，他们以前是
publishing new lines of the log file in
在以下位置发布日志文件的新行
the tail channel on the other end of
另一端的尾部通道
that I have a method here that's marked
我这里有一个标记的方法
up as a spring integration service
作为春季整合服务
activator and it is listening on tail
激活剂，它正在听尾巴
channel and it will handle basically
渠道，它将基本上处理
what it gets handed is the payload of
它得到的是
the message which is that line of data
信息就是那一行数据
and using a little groovy groovy string
并使用一些常规的常规字符串
magic I'm going to test and say there's
魔术，我要测试，说有
a containment that token of lightning
闪电般的收容物
data if so I want to calculate the
数据，如果这样我想计算
timestamp that's on the left-hand side
时间戳记在左侧
of that string in this case I this app
在这种情况下，我这个程序的字符串
I'm using go to time not the Java
我正在使用去时间而不是Java
standard time API is because they're
标准时间API是因为它们
just so much easier to work with so here
这么容易使用
I'm going to keep parsing that every
我将继续解析每个
time I get a new message this latest
我最近一次收到新消息的时间
value will update and keep updating this
值将更新并不断更新
timestamp which now any separate threat
现在有任何单独威胁的时间戳
of action I again I'm using springs
动作我再次使用弹簧
scheduling support and I have a
安排支持，我有一个
scheduled task over here that runs every
在这里运行的预定任务
5 seconds it's going to do a check what
5秒钟要检查一下
it's going to do it's going to calculate
它会去做它会去计算
what the current timestamp is and then
当前时间戳是多少，然后
it's going to calculate the difference
它会计算出差异
between now and when the latest piece of
从现在到最新的
lightning data was read in from the log
从日志中读取了闪电数据
file it says that if it's been more than
归档说如果已经超过
10 seconds we need to generate an alert
我们需要10秒钟来生成警报
you know flag it it's very bad and we're
你知道这很不好，我们
going to publish it we're going to
要发布它，我们要
convert and send it out to the topic
转换并发送给主题
status the duration has been less than
状态持续时间少于
10 seconds it's going to say now it's
现在要说10秒
good and send it to the same topic I may
好，然后将其发送给同一主题，我可能会
be wondering what so what is topic
想知道主题是什么
status what is this what kind of
状态这是什么样的
template is this if I scroll back I can
如果我向后滚动，模板就是这个
see we have a sent messaging template
看到我们有一个发送的消息传递模板
and sent messaging template is from
并且发送的消息传递模板来自
Springs the spring frameworks WebSockets
Springs Spring框架WebSockets
support layer the sense that say
支持层说
basically we have a we have a class of
基本上我们有一类
integration we have some WebSocket
集成我们有一些WebSocket
support so what we're going to do is
支持，所以我们要做的是
publish these messages to a WebSocket
将这些消息发布到WebSocket
and later on we will have a web layer
稍后我们将有一个网络层
that hooks into and can get the messages
钩住并可以获取消息
pushed out to a dynamic
推出动态
please some of this other stuff that I
请我其他一些东西
have in here like task scheduler and
在这里像任务计划程序一样
configure tasks this deals with the fact
配置与此事实有关的任务
that when you have more than one
当你有一个以上
component in the app context that is
应用上下文中的组件
involved with task scheduling Spring
参与任务调度Spring
Framework cannot resolve that for you so
框架无法为您解决问题
you have to get to figure out how to
你必须弄清楚如何
configure it and this essentially tells
配置它，这实际上告诉
WebSocket and the schedule annotations
WebSocket和计划注释
to both use the same task scheduler now
现在都使用相同的任务计划程序
I'm going to do is I'm going to jump to
我要做的就是跳到
the bottom here and then work my way up
在这里的底部，然后继续前进
because we're talking about pushing a
因为我们正在谈论推动
message out over a WebSocket this last
最后通过WebSocket发出消息
class is my WebSocket config if you
类是我的WebSocket配置，如果您
actually go to the spring dot io / guide
实际去spring dot io /指南
when you and if you search for WebSocket
当您以及如果您搜索WebSocket
you'll find a guide that actually walks
您会发现实际上可以行走的指南
you through how to set up WebSockets and
您将了解如何设置WebSocket和
it even talks about the stop messaging
它甚至谈论停止消息传递
protocol which I'll mention here further
协议，我将在这里进一步提及
on so essentially I use that guide to
在本质上，我使用该指南来
help you write this piece of code here
帮助您在此处编写这段代码
we're going to use again we're gonna use
我们将再次使用，我们将使用
groovy grape and pull in we need some
时髦的葡萄，我们需要一些
stomp WebSocket support in the browser
在浏览器中实现WebSocket支持
and we need some sock j/s which suck KS
我们需要一些袜子来吸KS
provides a graceful fallback in case the
提供一个优美的后备，以防
browser doesn't have WebSocket stored it
浏览器没有WebSocket存储
can fall back and still provide the same
可以退回并仍然提供相同的
effect and in this case I'm basically
效果，在这种情况下，我基本上
configuring the things and talk the
配置事物并谈论
broker is geared to talk to anything on
经纪人准备与任何事情谈
flash topic so you can have one channel
Flash主题，因此您可以拥有一个频道
you can have 50 different channels
您可以有50个不同的频道
essentially it's just part of its
本质上，这只是其一部分
protocol now it's geared here you know
协议现在适用于您，您知道
slash app is the destination that the
斜杠应用程序是
web wants to push something to the
网络希望将某些东西推送到
server side the server is looking at
服务器端服务器正在查看
slash app that's where I can find its
斜杠应用程序，在这里我可以找到它
material and then down here there's some
材料，然后在这里有一些
configuration and to Teletoon not only
配置和Teletoon不仅
register a WebSocket but also include
注册一个WebSocket但还包括
sock Jos fallback support it shouldn't
袜子乔斯的后备支持，它不应该
situation calls for it and you can find
情况需要它，你可以找到
more detailed description about what all
关于所有内容的详细说明
these settings mean in the getting
这些设置意味着
started guide that
开始指导
pulled up I'm going to go back here and
拉起我要回到这里
show the last two bits are here I have
显示最后两位在这里
basically a simple spring MVC controller
基本上是一个简单的spring MVC控制器
and I'm going to return back at the
然后我将返回
flash at the flasher out I'm going to
闪到闪光灯，我要去
look at the index template and then
看一下索引模板，然后
which should have my connection code and
应该有我的连接代码和
then finally have a tiny little POJO
然后终于有了一个小的POJO
here which just in the definition of
这里只是在定义
alarm which has the 13 description now
现在有13个说明的警报
that's one that's thanks for them the
那是对他们的感谢
other samples are but it contains a
其他样品是，但它包含一个
power pack a bunch of functionality in
电源包中的一堆功能
it now the whole time I've had my
现在整个我都拥有了
simulator running it's been generating
运行它正在生成的模拟器
stuff but now I think it's time to run
东西，但现在我认为是时候运行了
the monitor tool we just walked through
我们刚刚介绍的监控工具
we're gonna fire it up let's go to the
我们要把它火起来，让我们去
browser here local hosts refresh it so
浏览器在这里本地主机刷新它，所以
here we got a message displayed and
在这里，我们显示了一条消息，
defaults to zero and more traffic
默认为零，更多流量
happens we can expect this page
碰巧我们可以期待此页面
dynamically update so so far it still
到目前为止，动态更新
didn't zero seconds the timing on this
没有零秒的时间
see that something run in the background
看到在后台运行
don't we see we restarted here
我们没有看到我们在这里重新启动
make sure I don't have a lingering the
确保我没有缠绵
page open here on my spots okay let's
在这里打开页面，好吧，让我们
see you need to kind of refresh
看到你需要刷新
everything so right now good proof that
现在一切都很好地证明了
it's a live demo yeah so demo quickly
这是现场演示，所以请快速演示
without failures
没有失败
okay well exactly you know speaking of
好吧，确切地说，你知道
failures well let's go kill let's go
失败吧，走吧，杀了吧，走吧
kill the simulator let's imagine the
杀死模拟器让我们想象一下
production system died of sad death and
生产系统死于悲惨的死亡，
but nobody was there to see it because
但没人在那里看到它，因为
we're looking at the console so here in
我们正在看控制台，所以在这里
increments from four to nine seconds and
从4秒增加到9秒，
now it goes to 14 seconds and it's bad
现在到了14秒，这很糟糕
and so that is this could be the screen
所以这可能是屏幕
on your overhead projector in the ops
在操作中的投影仪上
center and right it's the customers
中心和正确的是客户
visiting you know it it turns red and
拜访您就知道它变成红色了，
whole thing is is you can say hey we're
整个事情是你可以说嘿我们
on top of it and you know you got your
最重要的是，你知道你得到了你的
floor team able to rush around and
地板小组能够奔波
figure out what's going wrong they they
找出他们出了什么问题
patched the system they swap out a
修补了他们换出的系统
server and it fired back up you know
服务器并触发备份你知道
without having you know with my hands
不知道你用我的双手
away from the keyboard it poof it goes
远离键盘，它会掉下去
back to green status and it's
回到绿色状态
everything's good so you know this right
一切都很好，所以你知道这个权利
here you know basically I grabbed a lot
在这里你知道我基本上抓住了很多
of different components and put them
不同的组件，并把它们
together and what I enjoyed about it is
在一起，我喜欢的是
well I know what spring integration does
好吧，我知道spring整合有什么用
and I know you know I know how to create
我知道你知道我会如何创造
some simple pojos to contain my data and
一些简单的pojos包含我的数据，
I like the alarm record and I know what
我喜欢警报记录，我知道
how to build some spring MVC pages and
如何构建一些Spring MVC页面以及
now we've got WebSocket support with
现在我们有了WebSocket支持
some you know and I was able to figure
一些你知道的，我能够弄清楚
out how to use that there are guides
找出如何使用，有指南
that I could roll it all together and
我可以将所有内容一起滚动
build a support tool with the toolset
使用工具集构建支持工具
that I already know and I wasn't
我已经知道但我不是
thinking in the terms of let me I need a
用我的角度思考，我需要一个
build file am I going to use Gradle am I
构建文件是我要使用Gradle吗？
going to use maven I didn't need to use
将要使用的Maven我不需要使用
either it would be this and I was able
要么就是这个，我就能
to you know do do some string
你知道做一些弦乐吗
manipulation parlor magic using groovy
使用Groovy操纵客厅魔术
if I tried to write that in Java be
如果我试图用Java编写
pulling my hair out
拉我的头发
so when there's a slip back here and
所以当这里有滑倒时
some of these things and you know what
其中一些事情，你知道什么
this emphasizes what your options are
这强调了您的选择
maybe you don't maybe you're starting to
也许你没有，也许你开始
realize this is the dopest support tool
意识到这是最重要的支持工具
but it's a support tool gets enough love
但这是一个获得足够爱的支持工具
and attention and you build it up it may
和关注，您可以建立它
actually become a micro service it might
实际上可能会成为微服务
join the suite of production tools and
加入生产工具套件，并
basically be pulled under the umbrella
基本上被拉到伞下
and people may essentially view as part
人们基本上可以将其视为
of the app I saw a slide the other day
前几天我看到的应用程序的幻灯片
that showed monolithic apps and micro
显示了单片应用程序和微型
services and strangely enough that had
服务，而且奇怪的是
to say I had all the same wheels at the
说我的车轮都一样
center it was just whether there was one
中心只是是否有一个
big box around all of it or whether they
周围是否有一个大盒子，或者是否
were all separate processes but the same
都是分开的过程，但都是一样的
fundamental concept that it's a bunch of
基本概念是一堆
services working together to support the
共同支持的服务
system you know to review the benefit
您知道的系统来审查收益
here with using spring boot is that you
在这里使用弹簧靴是你
know I get a build cool faster if I'm
我知道如果我
sitting in the OP Center I'm not working
坐在OP中心我不工作
on the perfect app so I want something
在完美的应用程序上，所以我想要一些东西
that's going to help me speed up my
那会帮助我加快我的速度
development time I definitely know that
开发时间我肯定知道
I'm using proven stack when you look at
当您查看时，我使用的是经过验证的堆栈
the math adoption of a spring framework
Spring框架的数学采用
and you look at the popularity and the
然后看看人气和
rise of Apache Tomcat and the download
Apache Tomcat的兴起和下载
rates on things like spring Buddhahood
像春天佛陀的利率
phenomenal to top it off of you know
惊人的超越它
these these are products that are
这些是这些产品
supported by solid team now I don't how
现在得到了坚实团队的支持
many years Tomcat has been out but you
Tomcat已经出很多年了，但是你
know that that's that's all develop we
知道那就是我们的全部发展
you know the spring team is there to
你知道春天队在那里
always crank out new solid rock-solid
总是发动新的坚如磐石
code and the big message here is I get a
代码，这里最大的消息是我得到了
finished writing these support tools
完成编写这些支持工具
sooner so when I do that I get to go
更快，所以当我这样做时，我就可以走了
back to my day time job and build more
回到我的日常工作，并建立更多
of those perfect apps or hope I can see
那些完美的应用程序，或者希望我能看到
if lightning will strike twice so
如果闪电会击中两次
well we got a bunch of good questions
好吧，我们有很多很好的问题
teed up okay so let's see uh first one
做好准备，好，让我们来看看第一个
um Jonathan asks he was curious when the
um Jonathan问他好奇的时候
release date on that learning spring
在那个学习春季发布日期
boot book that you were working on he's
您正在研究的入门书
curious when you were thinking what time
想知道什么时候会好奇
frame you were thinking about that
您正在考虑的框架
releasing uh they told me the tentative
释放，他们告诉我了
date for that would be around November
日期大约是十一月
well this is a cheap shot but you can
好吧，这是一个便宜的镜头，但是你可以
you can monitor I try to blog about it
你可以监视我尝试写博客
pretty often and if you go to my
经常，如果你去我的
personal blog site
个人博客网站
I'm not that how readable that is I have
我不是那么有可读性
a category and track my track the
类别并跟踪我的足迹
progress on it but it's on a on a tight
进度，但紧迫
turnaround you're not going to wait two
周转，你不会等待两个
years for this book to come out what
年这本书出来什么
cost some Peaks added and stuff like
花费了一些山峰和类似的东西
that but so hopefully by I was hoping
那个，但如此希望我希望
they would have it done by spring once I
他们一旦我春天就会完成
could be in enough to pre copies but
可能足以预复印，但
unfortunately that's not the case go ah
不幸的是不是这样啊
well well we'll just have to hand out
好吧，我们只需要分发
free copy of the spring data book um
春季数据手册的免费副本um
let's see okay um another question from
让我们看看好吧，还有一个问题
Daniel and he asks is it possible to
丹尼尔，他问是否有可能
parameterize the scheduled annotation
参数化计划的注释
without having to declare being in XML
无需声明使用XML
for it it takes a cron expression but it
为此，它需要一个cron表达式，但是
must be determined at compile time I'd
必须在编译时确定
like to know if I could use expression
想知道我是否可以使用表达
defining a config file I'm not sure
定义一个我不确定的配置文件
about that one that's that's a very good
关于那是一个非常好的
question would I have the and while
问题我有和
you're there a very quick question
你有一个非常快速的问题
someone was saying hey what shall what
有人说嘿怎么办
we're using to launch those app doc Ruby
我们正在使用这些应用程序文档Ruby
files the spring shell and I responded
提交弹簧壳，我回应
by saying it was the boot command-line
通过说它是引导命令行
interface which I believe it is is that
我相信的界面是
right
对
uh yeah this is um I'm meeting this in
嗯，这是嗯，我正在开会
this uh globe
这个呃地球
that's one way yeah I haven't actually
是的，是的，我实际上还没有
be using a GD M we have those um okay
使用GD M，我们有那些嗯
I'm using G VM is the means to install
我正在使用G VM进行安装
what's called the spring boot tool and
所谓的弹簧启动工具和
the
的
the name of the actual command is called
实际命令的名称称为
spring but there's also a homebrew
春天，但也有自制酒
recipe if you want it you can do brew
食谱，如果你想要的话，你可以冲泡
install books spring food should say
装书春季食品应该说
it's brew tap I think it's like a type
这是自来水我想这是一种
it yeah the little clap tap you know and
是的，你会拍拍一下
then brew this is on a Mac a brew
然后在Mac上酿造
install spring boot the the brew is a
安装弹簧靴，酿造是
popular package manager for the back but
受欢迎的包装经理，但
g.b.m is on a lot of platforms so if you
GBM在很多平台上都可以使用
install gbms click one to the long side
安装gbms单击长边
anyway JDM tool net okay I was wrong
反正JDM工具网好吧，我错了
with the typo there you go this is this
有错别字，这是这个
is a popular tool the groovy community
是groovy社区的流行工具
because you can manage lots there's this
因为你可以管理很多事情
is a listing of the products that you
是您的产品清单
can get through it and it's new release
可以通过它，它是新版本
with these tools come out your gvm will
有了这些工具，您的gvm将会
update you can download install on
您可以下载安装的更新
things like Grails groovy Gradle and
像Grails groovy Gradle和
usually within 24 hours of a new spring
通常在新春天的24小时内
boot released they get the CLI on here
引导释放，他们在这里获取CLI
now this this is not the place to get
现在这不是去的地方
the like char files if you're using a
像char文件（如果您使用的是
product you know if you're building a
您知道是否要建立产品
spring boot application and using maven
Spring Boot应用程序和使用Maven
or Gradle to get the boot libraries this
或Gradle获取启动库
is to get the spring boots CLI app and a
是要获得 spring boot CLI应用程序和一个
list on where the the supported
列出支持的位置
platforms it has but gotcha and so you
平台，但有陷阱，所以你
so you are in fact using the spring boot
所以你实际上是在使用弹簧靴
CLI to launch these you know the the dot
CLI启动这些你知道的点
app files all right exactly involves
应用程序文件完全可以涉及
excuse me yeah and what you know comes
对不起，你知道的是什么
loaded with a ton of features and I'm
充满了很多功能，我
using the run because it's letting me
使用跑步，因为它让我
prototype and run stuff but it actually
原型和运行的东西，但实际上
has the capability to take your tool and
有能力拿走你的工具
turn it into an executable jar file so
把它变成可执行的jar文件
once you hammer out your support app you
敲定支持应用程序后，
can turn it into an executable jar file
可以将其转换为可执行的jar文件
stick it on a thumb drive and carry out
将其粘贴在拇指驱动器上并执行
your op Center and deploy it wherever
您的运营中心，并将其部署到任何地方
you find a JVM
你找到一个JVM
nice excellent okay so back to Daniels
很好，很好，回到丹尼尔斯
question about the parameterised at
关于参数化的问题
schedule annotation Joanne you repeat
日程注释Joanne您重复
the question real quick sorry if you
这个问题真的很抱歉，如果你
take it I think your question was is it
接受，我想你的问题是
possible to is it possible to
有可能
parameterize this I don't know how to
参数化这个，我不知道如何
use expression he wants to use an
使用他想使用的表达
expression to find it in a config file
表达式以在配置文件中找到它
yeah I I don't know that one yeah I
是的，我不知道那个我
don't think they talked about that in
不要以为他们在谈论
the guide we have one guide that talks
该指南，我们有一个讲
about scheduling tasks I don't remember
关于安排我不记得的任务
that being mentioned as an option we may
被提及为一种选择，我们可能
have two meant to take an action to try
有两个打算采取行动尝试
to answer that I think around here with
回答我在这里想的
a hyperlinks here they talked about it
他们在这里谈论的超链接
talks about three options on scheduling
讨论日程安排的三个选项
a fixed rate fixed delay or cron
固定利率固定时延或cron
expression it takes you right to the
表达它带你去的权利
spring Java Docs to talk about it but
Spring Java Docs谈论它，但是
meant to ping either either jurgen or
旨在对Jurgen或ping通
Dave cider to ask them if it's
戴夫苹果酒问他们是否
injectable from a property file because
可从属性文件中注入，因为
that I mean that would be very
我的意思是说
convenient in my book but I don't do it
我的书很方便，但我不这样做
Daniel maybe Daniel maybe just follow
丹尼尔也许丹尼尔也许只是跟随
Greg on one Twitter and you guys can can
格雷格在一个Twitter上，你们可以
link up once once we figure out the
一旦确定了链接一次
answer
回答
I mean detail to that um let's see uh
我是说那个细节，让我们来看看
yeah I think yes Christopher Smith thank
是的，我想是克里斯托弗·史密斯
you very much for popping up the gbm's
您非常喜欢弹出gbm
well I just didn't didn't see that
好吧，我只是没有没看到
before
之前
um okay let's see so Christopher by the
嗯，好的，让我们来看看克里斯托弗
way also comments and says hey the
方式还评论说，嘿
source for the handler directly parses
处理程序的源直接解析
the annotation values quant expression
批注值量化表达式
no spring expression language um FYI so
没有春季表达语言，仅供参考
um but oh cool got some discussion going
嗯，但是很酷，有一些讨论在进行
on here um another another photo another
在这里，另一张照片，另一张
guy Ben is saying that you can parameter
家伙本说你可以参数
the con value like anything else with a
与其他任何东西一样的con值
spell expression from properties so
从属性中拼写表达，以便
it sounds it sounds like if this this
听起来好像是这个
one's on the bubble you know let's let's
一个人在泡沫上，你知道，让我们
get the official word from mom from from
从
David and of course your again and you
大卫，当然还有你，你
know gentlemen just follow on Twitter
知道先生们只要关注Twitter
follow Greg on Twitter and he'll post
在Twitter上关注Greg，他将发布
the answer on so that you'll see it on
答案就可以了
otherwise you can get in touch with Greg
否则，您可以与Greg联系
by the various methods that you see here
通过您在这里看到的各种方法
on this slide
在这张幻灯片上
um and I just want to take this
嗯，我只想吃这个
opportunity to let you know that this is
机会让您知道这是
being recorded if you want to share it
如果您要分享，将被录制
with your colleagues on you know passing
与你的同事一起知道过去
around the office we will be posting it
在办公室周围，我们将发布它
on YouTube as always um and if you want
一如既往地在YouTube上发布，如果您愿意
to notified when that is available just
通知何时可用
grab um you know go to either thing that
抓住你知道的东西
IO /blog to subscribe to the atom feed
IO / blog订阅原子供稿
or you can go to spring audio / video if
或者您可以转到春季音频/视频，如果
you just want the videos because that's
你只想要视频，因为那是
the YouTube channel you can subscribe to
您可以订阅的YouTube频道
the YouTube channel there on if you
那里的YouTube频道
subscribe to the blog though you'll get
订阅博客，尽管您会得到
a bunch of other great content obviously
一堆其他很棒的内容
all the engineering blogs spring one
所有工程博客春一
session replays and etcetra etcetra
会话重播和etcetra etcetra
etcetra least news that sort of things
至少不了解这类新闻
there's a lot of value there if you're
如果您有很多价值
if you're interested to to check it out
如果您有兴趣检查一下
um great so just want to invite you to
很好，只想邀请您参加
join some of our upcoming webinars we've
加入我们即将举行的一些在线研讨会
got some cool stuff coming up this month
这个月有一些很棒的东西
as well and we will be taking a break in
以及，我们将休息一下
the month of August for the summer
夏季的八月
holiday so they won't be any webinars in
放假，这样他们就不会参加任何网络研讨会了
August but on please do come back and
8月，但请务必回来，
join us we are going to be having a
加入我们，我们将拥有一个
number of webinars in the next couple on
接下来的几场网络研讨会的数量
next couple weeks here um the one of
接下来的几周，这里是
them if you've never heard of this guy
他们，如果你从未听说过这个家伙
he's really good his name is Michael
他真的很好他叫迈克尔
Bluth he's going to be talking about the
布卢斯（Bluth）他将谈论
howdy how he makes the case for spring
你好，他如何为春季辩护
to his clients he's an independent
对他的客户来说，他是独立的
consultant um he's kind of out there in
顾问，他在外面
the speaker circuit a lot and that's on
扬声器电路很多，并且一直在
July 22nd so I'm not going to go so far
7月22日，所以我不会走那么远
as say is
就像是
the business case for spring but it
春天的商业案例，但它
really makes a great technology you know
确实使您知道一项伟大的技术
gives you a good gives you some good
给你带来好处给你带来好处
ammunition on how to make that case for
关于如何提出理由的弹药
spring with a couple business points
春天有几个业务要点
kind of sprinkled in there so that's in
有点撒在里面，所以在
July 22nd on on July 15th um from the
从7月22日至7月15日
absolutely insane project files these
绝对疯狂的项目文件这些
poor guys Casey and Phil got tasked with
可怜的人凯西和菲尔受命与
building a shopping cart in 24 hours on
在24小时内建立购物车
using spring and they actually pulled it
用弹簧，他们实际上拉了它
off so on if you just like reading these
如果您喜欢阅读这些内容，请依此类推
sort of sadistic stories of core people
核心人物的虐待狂故事
who get tasked with ridiculous
那些荒谬的任务
requirements and then actually pull it
要求然后实际拉
at all pull it out with sprinkle win on
一点点地把它洒出来
this is kind of a war story from the
这是一个关于战争的故事
field here might be might be of interest
这里的字段可能是您感兴趣的
to you on also on July 29th we're going
同样在7月29日向您发送
to rust dinner from crafter software
用手工艺软件制作晚餐
talking about content management on web
谈论网络上的内容管理
and mobile using spring and Ruby and
并使用spring和Ruby进行移动
then like I said we'll be taking August
就像我说过我们要参加八月
off um so with that um just wanted to
嗯，所以那个那个只是想
kick it back to you Greg any kind of
格雷格把它踢回你
closing comments before we before we
在我们之前结束评论
sign off it doesn't look like there's
签收它看起来不像
any more questions from our attendees at
来自我们与会者的其他问题
the moment well I just want to encourage
那一刻我只想鼓励
anybody that I I've found that this this
我发现的这个人
platinum a development really it really
铂金真的是真的发展
has to civil to it that I look for when
我一直在寻找
manager comes to me and says hey can you
经理来找我说你能
prototype something and come back to me
制作一些原型然后回到我身边
in 24 hours and give me report on it and
在24小时内给我报告
I can go try something out I can tinker
我可以去尝试一些我可以修补的东西
with it and I don't have to deal with a
用它，我不必处理
lot of overhead and I can find something
很多开销，我可以找到一些东西
to hate I think that you know this may
讨厌我认为你知道这可能
be the answer you're looking for or this
就是您要寻找的答案或这个
may be the tool you're looking for and
可能是您正在寻找的工具，
down the road I can polish it up and
在路上我可以擦亮，
actually may become part of the app I'm
实际上可能会成为我所使用的应用程序的一部分
not I don't have this dichotomy of well
不，我没有这种二分法
I built you know I built the quick
我建立了你知道我建立了快速
prototype and Python but now I need to
原型和Python，但现在我需要
migrate it into Java to add it to the
将其迁移到Java中以将其添加到
app or I need to tell the DevOps team
应用程序，或者我需要告诉DevOps团队
they now need to deal hi thon and Java
他们现在需要对付thon和Java
instead with one cohesive ecosystem here
而是这里有一个凝聚力的生态系统
I can pull off some some crafty support
我可以提供一些狡猾的支持
features
特征
and by basing it on spring boot you know
通过将其置于弹簧靴上，您知道
even though spring boot is relatively
即使 spring boot 相对
due on you know it's its heritage is
由于你知道它的遗产是
quite mature and you know we're running
很成熟，你知道我们正在跑步
it in production ourselves actually with
它实际上在生产中与
our DevOps team you know on the spring
我们在春季认识的DevOps团队
i/o website I wish you know gets quite a
I / O网站，希望您知道
lot of traffic you know in the millions
数以百万计的您知道的流量
of music visitors per month so not a not
每月的音乐访问者数量，所以不是
a rinky-dink amount of traffic or
少量的流量或
rinky-dink application by any means and
以任何方式使用皱纹粉红色的应用
uh something that our our customers are
呃，我们的客户是
actually using already production on at
实际使用已经在生产
large company so boots a good good
大公司，所以靴子很好
foundation arms for that purpose Greg
为此目的的基础武器Greg
thanks a lot great talk and yeah I think
非常感谢大家的精彩演讲，是的，我认为
this is this is very cool especially
这是非常酷的
curved kind of a mic you know people who
弯曲的麦克风，你知道的人
are looking at micro-services for how to
正在寻找微服务，以了解如何
build these kind of lightweight you know
建立这些轻量级的
monitoring and management tools um super
监控和管理工具um super
quick and you know with not a lot of
快速，您知道的很多
code so pretty impressive thank you very
代码非常令人印象深刻，非常感谢
much alright everyone um see you next
好吧，大家嗯，下次见
time I'll see you to one of the webinars
有时间我会见你参加网络研讨会之一
in the future have a great today and
未来的今天很棒
thanks for your time and attention bye
感谢您的时间和关注，再见
everybody
大家
you
您